http://www.sextoy.co.nz/policies/privacy-policy

Adults only (18+)
This website contains adult material and is only suitable for those 18 years or older. Click Enter only if you are at least 18 years of age.
Privacy policy
The House of fun is committed to protecting your privacy.
This privacy statement discloses what information we gather about you when you visit the The House of fun website and describes how we use that information. Our policy is to keep the personal information we receive from our website completely confidential and used solely for internal purposes. We will not share your personal information with any other parties.
Collection of your Personal Information:
The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, e-mail, phone. We may collect certain information about your visit, such as type of browser you use; the date and time you access the website; the pages that you access while at the website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website. This information is used to help improve and administer the website.
Use of your Personal Information:
The personal information collected on this website will be used to provide the services you have requested. We may use your personal information to provide you with important product updates and new services offered.
Security:
The House of fun employs up-to-date Secure Socket Layer Technology (SSL) to encrypt your information and help make sure that your information is kept safe. Some Web browsers and some firewalls do not permit a secure connection. If your browser will not permit a secure connection, you can use a standard server connection to complete your transaction, but this method is not guaranteed to be secure. To discover whether your browser is in secure mode during the checkout process, check that a lock or a key icon is displayed in the lower left-hand corner of your browser window. You can also check by looking at the URL bar on top of your browser. This line will typically show the first characters as "https" when a secure connection has been established rather than "http" which indicates a connection that is not secured.
Questions:
If you have any questions about this Statement or concerns about the way we process your Personal Data, please contact us using the Contact Us form.
We may occasionally modify this privacy statement. All such changes will be reflected on this web page.
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
